Take a sip of blue water, access the frequency of manifestation and get ready, because this
video is the most powerful you will see on this platform.
I will now teach you the four steps to definitively activate the infinite power of your subconscious
mind with the law of attraction.
Your life will never be the same after this.
Have you had your blue water yet?
Then our commitment, leave a like, press this thumbs up here and let's get started.
Have you heard of Nikola Tesla?
I really like Tesla.
I have a strong connection with the numbers 369.
Tesla said that if you knew the power and magnificence of the numbers 369, you would
have the keys that open the doors of the universe.
Now there is another quote from Nikola Tesla that I want to open this content of ours and
I want you to reflect on because this quote will completely change your reality.
I dare to challenge you.
After this video, your life will never be the same again, so write to me here in the
comments the day and time you are watching this video, because that day and that time
will be a milestone in your history.
And if you haven't subscribed to the channel yet, subscribe, because you will come back
here to tell me everything that happened in your life after this video.
Let's go to the quote for Tesla.
If you want to know the secrets of the universe, think in terms of energy, frequency and vibration.
I'm sure you've heard that the energy you emit attracts everything you have in your
life.
People, events, opportunities, experiences, all of this resonates with your vibration.
And that's true.
And why does this happen?
You will understand and will begin to comprehend how you can attract what you want into your
life and not what you no longer want.
This happens because your thoughts are electromagnetic waves of energy that cross time and space.
What you are thinking at this moment is generating a feeling.
What you are feeling now is a reflection of what is already manifesting in the quantum
field and also in your physical and material life.
This is the quantum entanglement.
Your thoughts are like I, they expand to the universe.
You have a supercharger.
Have you ever realized this?
You are made in the image and likeness of the creator.
And it is not physical, otherwise we would all be the same.
God is perfect.
Right here in the comments like this, look, God is perfect.
He created us perfectly and we co-create reality with him.
It all starts with our subconscious, which is our link with creation.
Our thoughts are like magnets.
They expand to the flow field, the universal quantum field.
And they attract thoughts with a similar vibration.
So you think, organize yourself in the field and attract similar things.
This is called the law of attraction.
Everything comes back to you two loaded with the same.
That is why I talk about the danger of complaining.
And in my book, there is, look, the new code of manifestation.
Tell me in the comments if you've read the new manifestation code.
I'll give it to you as a gift if you do something here.
Wait a minute, who doesn't have it yet?
Here's what I'll say.
All reality that exists in the universe can be created by you.
This means that you also have a share of responsibility for what continues to happen in your life.
This book is the official teaching material for my channel, Edson Berger, The Manifestation Club.
And if you don't have it yet, stay with me here until the end of this video, because I'm going to give it to you as a gift.
It's for sale on Amazon.
It's one of the most read books on the law of attraction in Brazil at the moment.
If you want, I'll give it to you as a gift.
You don't need to buy it on Amazon, because subscribers, you have to subscribe here on the channel,
subscribers get it as a gift and you can even choose whether you want a physical or digital version.
So, stay with me here until the end.
There's a book called "The Law of Attraction".
In this book it is clearly stated, your attention to the themes, your activation of thoughts and the response of the law of attraction to these thoughts are responsible for each person,
each event and each circumstance that comes into your life.
I see some people saying, "The law of attraction doesn't work for me, I've already done everything", no, you didn't do everything.
In fact, everything you did made exactly what happened happened.
The law of attraction works all the time for everyone.
You couldn't change the essential.
You'll understand here, look, everything that comes to you enters through a magnetic vibrational funnel,
because the universe responds by resonance and not by merit.
But here's a truth that many people still don't understand.
You don't attract exactly what you think, you attract what you resonate with.
In other words, thought is the beginning of the process.
And that is why the people who manifest faster are not those who think more, they are not those who use more techniques, they are those who learn to adjust their vibration daily.
They learn to tune their electromagnetic signals to what they want to manifest and they do it.
This every day, I was fat, sick, obese, with an eviction order, I sought repossession in my small block.
At the time, I decided to take on a challenge, a challenge to create a new reality for my life.
And that's exactly what I'm doing with you who are already in the manifestation club group with the new reality challenge.
Tell me here in the comments, how many days have you been participating in the new reality challenge?
If this video found you today, it was no coincidence.
You can say, hey, I'm starting now because you're going to enter a new era in your life.
This new reality challenge is where you practice the activations.
Blue water is a neuro-linguistic programming, neuroscience and law of attraction technique.
With the blue water technique, we can access a neural network of a very strong emotion, of having already achieved what we want.
We also have the manifestation card that is transforming people's lives.
The most powerful tool of the law of attraction, when we use the morning miracle technique together with blue water and also repeat the affirmations of the new reality.
Let's write here in the comments, write here for me, everything is already resolved.
I'm already prosperous, the universe conspires in my favor.
I'm already the person who lives this reality, everything works out for me.
All these techniques together have the goal of raising your vibration to a very high level.
And here comes the secret.
When you achieve what you are achieving with me, which is to sustain the vibration, you collapse the quantum field and everything you want starts to accelerate, your reality starts to change at a frightening speed.
It's like gravity, it's always in action.
Let me take this pen, for example, look, if I let go, it will fall.
Regardless of whether I believe it or not, even if you don't realize it, gravity is working.
As you know, the law of attraction is the most powerful force in the universe and it is always in constant action, just like any other universal law.
But there is a detail, just like gravity is always present, even if you are not aware of it, the law of attraction is too.
It works all the time, with or without your permission, with or without your attention.
It's like a boomerang, have you ever seen a boomerang?
Everything you think generates feelings, if you don't take care of your thoughts, you attract bad things into your life.
Everything you think generates feelings, you emanate them, you attract them.
That's why I say, those who complain, complain three times, they thought, they threw it to the universe, they attracted it.
What's the problem, for example, if you think about bad things that happened in your life.
Oh, I'm remembering that past that hurt.
Oh, my God, life is bad luck.
The universe takes more situations to give you more of that.
No, I'm not here to make fun of those who suffered.
That little voice was mine.
What I'm saying is the following, there's no point in suffering again or putting myself in a victim position.
I'll only attract more of the same.
I need to turn off that little voice inside me.
I don't know if you've ever studied neurolinguistic programming.
NLP, I'm going to hold an event on June 7.
If you're in my manifestation club group, you'll find out how to participate. If you're not in the group, stay with me until the end.
I'm going to do a technique in which, no matter what happened to you in the past, we're going to turn off that emotion of suffering so we can stop emitting that signal and stop receiving bad things because of what has already happened to us.
Another thing, imagine the following, look, this is the rule of the universe, look.
I receive the blow, then I vibrate at the frequency of the blow, I suffer at the frequency of the blow.
The universe says, okay, take more.
I emit, the universe says, okay, take more.
Many times this happens when the person, the woman who says she has a bad hand, for example, she receives a man who will really be the man she believes, right?
He's an unfaithful man, a dishonest man with her, without values. Then she emits that emotion and takes more.
Another man like him shows up and gets more. Or the person wants to be mugged, sends a signal and gets more mugged.
What's the secret?
I got hit, I need to turn off this vibration.
There's a technique for this, stay with me, just as I need to turn off the emotion of the past, I need to turn off the emotion of the present, I need to learn to connect to the frequency of the vibration of what I want to receive. What you think, you attract. That's what the law teaches.
There's an author, I don't know if you've heard of her, tell me here, you've heard of her, called Christ Whitman.
She states that we are all energetic beings, sending signals all the time and every day.
We send signals through what we say, what we do, what we think, what we feel and mainly what we believe.
Even through jokes. We say things in a joking tone, we are sending out a signal and we are attracting.
Every form of energy carries a vibration and this vibration comes into contact with other vibrations of the same nature.
That's how we create or attract experiences into our lives.
So, if you want to be a master of the law of attraction, you first need to master another law, the law of vibration.
That's why I'm telling you, if you don't have my book yet, I'm going to do the following.
I'm going to leave the link in the description of this video and pin it in the comments.
If you don't have it yet, you can get it for free.
It's a gift from me to you, physical or digital.
It's up to you, tell me in the comments if you want the physical or digital version.
Click on this link now and get the book.
Remember, to do this, you need to subscribe to the channel.
The law of vibration is perhaps one of the least known laws, but perhaps the most crucial.
That's why I talk much more about the law of vibration here in the book than about the law of attraction itself.
Because I need to understand the process of vibration in order to be able to attract things with the law of attraction.
The law of vibration states that everything is in motion and nothing remains still.
And it shows us something simple and powerful, like attracts light.
That's why you tend to be surrounded by people who are similar to you.
People who vibrate in an emotional range close to yours, people who reflect aspects of your own energy.
And it is precisely your current vibration that determines what is happening in your life right now.
Want to know what frequency you are vibrating at right now?
Simple. Observe your emotions.
Stop and feel what you have been feeling in the last few days.
Want to predict your own future?
Look at your last six months.
What frequency you vibrated at.
That is exactly what you will attract in your future.
Oh, Edson, I'm scared. Not me, I didn't vibrate. Cool.
You can change.
There is time to rotate. Always.
There are many ways for you to continue living the same life, but there is only one way to change, one and only way,
which is to change your frequency.
If you are feeling good, you are probably vibrating in the range of gratitude, joy, peace or enthusiasm.
Watching this video, your vibration has probably already risen since the beginning.
These emotions put you at a high frequency and radically increase your power of attraction.
For example, tell me here if you are doing a miracle morning technique.
I send it every day to my group at the manifestation club.
In the morning miracle technique, we start the day by raising our vibration to the top towards gratitude.
It is impossible not to vibrate high by doing the gratitude miracle technique.
Now, if you are feeling anger, fear, guilt, frustration, this indicates a low vibration frequency.
In the book here, I explained that there are two types of frequency. Jesus taught this in Matthew chapter 13 verse 1.
He says that whoever has more, more will be given to him and he will have an abundance.
This is the person who is in a high vibration, which I call the plus code.
And he says that whoever has less, more will be taken from him and everything he has left will be taken from him.
Whoever is in a low vibration, has a minus code.
And the universe will respond proportionally, illness, scarcity, blockages, mediocrity.
But this is the essential point.
New code, I explained that these frequencies form these two distinct fields, minus code and plus code.
In the minus code, the one at the bottom, your life is contracted and you feel emotions of shame, guilt and scarcity.
The code expands you, connects you, elevates you.
And that's exactly what Jesus explained in Matthew chapter 13 verse 1.
I'll repeat it for you.
The more you have, the more will be given to you and you will have an abundance.
Don't you want to be the one who has the most, who will be given the most and have an abundance?
In other words, the more you vibrate in abundance, the more abundance you have.
The more you give thanks, the more reasons you have to be thankful.
Write it here like this, the more I give thanks, the more reasons I have to be thankful.
Write it here in the comments.
That's why at the manifestation club, our focus is not on measuring your frequency.
Our focus is on raising your frequency every day.
My job is to raise your frequency.
It's my mission, it's my life, that's what I do every day.
And we do this through the techniques of the miracle morning, blue water and affirmations.
We also have the law of attraction boosted technique, sleeping with the law of attraction,
the envelope we are making now, putting it under our pillow every night, with the manifestation letter,
with the code that everything is possible, because it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter where you are vibrating now,
it doesn't matter where you are at the moment you came across this video.
If you came across this video, a sign from the universe, that things are starting to change and work out for you,
I'm going to make you a promise.
Starting today, your life will enter a new era.
A new era in which things are starting to work out.
Everything is starting to work out for you.
The universe is starting to conspire in your favor.
Remember, everything, everything in the universe is energy.
And energy is in constant movement.
It is not created, it is not destroyed, it only transforms.
It is present everywhere, at all times, and it never stops, it never sleeps, it never rests.
Quantum physics, have you heard of quantum physics?
It is my great passion, it is what transformed my life, I have been studying quantum physics for many years.
Where are the people from C.A.R. 369, from our community Attracting Wealth 369?
Write it down here like this, look, IMC 369.
If you are watching this video and you still haven't received the invitation to join C.A.R. 369, don't worry, do it like this, look.
One day you will receive the invitation.
Inside the C.R. there is a film called Who Are We?
Have you watched it? It is a film that talks about quantum physics, it teaches quantum physics in a playful, fun way.
Quantum physics teaches us that everything that exists in matter, including you, is made of vortices of energy spinning, vibrating, pulsating.
Each cell, each atom, each particle in your body emits a unique frequency.
It is your vibrational signature.
And if you observe honestly, you will realize, you are energy, you are vibration, you are frequency in motion.
God is perfect, God created it this way.
And do you know what raises this vibration?
Focus, commitment, clarity, code more.
He who has more, more will be given to him and he will have in abundance.
When you are focused like a laser beam, when you are truly committed to the goal, when you turbocharge the law of attraction,
when you travel to the future and you feel that the things you have chosen for your life are already real,
you activate trillions of cells within you in this field that you activate begins to collapse the external field and create the new reality.
That is why everything is in harmony with this frequency.
And everything when it is in harmony with this new frequency begins to move in your direction.
In the book The New Manifestation Code, I teach there.
All reality is shaped by your vibrational signature.
When you resonate with the reality you have chosen, you become the cause and no longer the effect.
There's an author I really like called Lois Ray.
She says the following, "Our thoughts have energy and creative power similar to that."
Through the law of attraction, your thoughts shape your experiences.
But that's not all.
All of us, at some level, carry a limiting inner voice.
It's a little voice that sometimes says, "Oh, you're not good enough."
"This isn't for you. This is a rich person's thing. You don't deserve it, you're not capable."
You're dreaming too big, quote, "Hm. I created this little voice to mess with this little voice that was inside me, to take away its power."
"We learn this in neurolinguistic programming. Mark it on your calendar, okay? You have an appointment with me."
On the 7th of the 6th, June 7th, June 7th, 8am, it will be from 8am to 6pm.
You need to join my manifestation club group to find out how to participate.
The awakening of the power of the mind will happen for a whole day, from 8am to 6pm, and you will live the most incredible experience of your life.
We will turn off that little voice, because that little voice is a legacy of traumas, stories, beliefs and codes that you have learned to repeat, but it is not you.
On June 7th, we will erase painful memories from the past. We will turn off fears, traumas, phobias.
We will learn to transform our habits, change our frequency and change our reality.
That is why it is the awakening of the power of the mind.
And here is a truth that can change everything.
If you leave this video with this truth, you will leave here a new person.
A high frequency, positive thought that generates a high frequency emotion, which generates a high vibration, activated with awareness and repetition, has more power than a thousand unconscious negative thoughts.
That is why, even though you cannot control your mind all the time, when you start to control it, you will start to have extraordinary results.
Therefore, understand, you are co-creating your reality all the time.
Even now, as you watch this video, you are omitting signals, frequencies and thoughts.
Life does not stop, creation never pauses.
Manifestation does not wait for your consent.
There is only one truth.
You are either creating consciously or not.
There is no vibrational neutrality.
You are always creating.
And here is something that needs to be said clearly.
Just because you don't know does not mean that the law of attraction stops working.
As I said, it is the same as gravity.
If I let go of the pen, it will fall, regardless of whether I believe in the law of gravity or not.
And the big mistake of those who suffer is to think that they are victims of chance.
In the book, "The New Code of Manifestation", tell me here if you have already picked up the book.
All reality that exists in the universe can be created by you, co-created, because you co-create with God and God is perfect.
And this brings with it a vibrational responsibility.
Understand, you are not guilty, guilty for everything that happened to you,
but you are responsible for what you choose to keep in the field, because everything that you feed with attention grows.
And now that you understand this fantastic power of vibration, I'm going to give you the four steps to activate the law of attraction with the power of your subconscious in a conscious way.
And here's a secret.
Each step is connected to the seven keys of the law of attraction that I teach in my book, "The New Manifestation Code".
Step number one, decide what you want.
Start there.
Start drawing what the life of your dreams looks like.
Isn't that what we put in the manifestation letter?
Tell me here if you made the letter, if you're putting it under your pillow every day.
If you haven't done it yet, do it like this, look.
Relax.
You're going to get the book that's in the description of this video.
You're going to receive an invitation to join the manifestation club group.
Read all the messages and you'll discover how to make this letter, okay?
Where do you want to live?
Who do you want to be with?
How much money do you want to have in your account?
You need to decide clearly with intention.
This is the key to the law of attraction that I teach in the book, the key to the law of attraction number one, decide.
And along with it in this first step, there is key number two, which is to ask clearly.
The universe responds to vibrational precision.
You only manifest what is clear and what you are vibrating coherently.
Step number two, feel worthy!
Once again, the law of attraction technique boosted with the manifestation card, it is perfect, which we are doing every night before going to sleep.
If you are not in the group yet, you are missing out.
But you have to subscribe to the channel, okay?
And remember, I am watching, there are people who are watching this video here on my channel and are not liking it.
So, what am I going to do with you, huh?
Give that thumbs up right away.
You only attract what you believe you deserve.
If there is doubt, guilt, shame or self-sabotage inside you, the field locks up.
This is the moment to activate the key to the law of attraction number three, manifesting as if it were already real.
This is what we did in the law of attraction technique boosted with the manifestation card.
And then you will let go and trust.
Only those who have faith can let go.
So the process of manifestation is to believe as if it were already real.
Number three, and key four is to let go.
You vibrate reality and then surrender without obsession, without anxiety, without fear.
Step number three, give thanks before the evidence.
It is believing in order to see.
Gratitude is the vibrational shortener of the journey.
When you give thanks, as if you had already received, you accelerate the manifestation.
This is the key to the law of attraction number five, look, what I teach here, thank before, gratitude is not a response.
Gratitude is construction.
And step four, act towards what you desire.
The law of attraction requires movement.
You do not attract only with intention.
Oh, I'm going to sit here meditating that money will fall from the sky.
It is not like that.
You only attract with intention, you attract with energy, you attract with action.
That is why the key to the law of attraction number six is to act, act with intention.
And it connects with key number seven, which is to receive
because manifestation is not an event.
It is a lifestyle.
It is a cycle.
That's why we're in the manifestation club.
And if you want to delve deeper into all of this, all of this is happening within the new reality challenge, which goes until June 7th.
When we close with the awakening of the power of the mind.
It's free, it's daily, and it's happening in the group.
How do you join the group?
You get the link in the video description here, look.
In the description of this video, you have the link, get the book, you can also pin it in the comments.
You get the physical or digital book.
It's in the description of the video pinned in the comments.
There's the link.
You click, go there, get the book, join the group and they're all send you all the information.
Remember that here on the channel, there's a new video every Tuesday and Thursday at noon.
And Sunday live at 11 11 in our manifestation club awakening, our weekly live meeting.
Here we're going to reach the highest vibration to achieve all of our dreams.
So do it now.
Take a sip of the blue water.
Remember.
Leave your like here.
Share this video because we will go together on this incredible journey of transformation of the demonstration club.
No.